Guide to the Class of 1907, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1907, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, records
1963-1970
RU 490
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.77
(7 boxes)
The records consist of reunion motion pictures and correspondence documenting the Yale Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1907 and its secretary, Warner S. (Misty) Hayes.
Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1907
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-B (YRG 10-B), Records of Sheffield Scientific School classes.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of reunion motion pictures and correspondence documenting the Yale Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1907 and its secretary, Warner S. (Misty) Hayes.
Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1907
- Reunions [motion pictures], 1927-1962; Series I
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - 20th reunion, 1927; film reel (16mm) (Box 1)
    - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 1D)
  - Reunion, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 2)
  - 20th reunion, 1927; film reel (16mm) (Box 3)
  - 20th, 25th, and 30th reunions, 1927, 1932, 1937; film reel (16mm) (Box 4)
    - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 4D)
  - 40th and 45th reunions?, 1947, 1952; film reel (16mm) (Box 5)
  - Reunion, Undated; film reel (16mm) (Box 6)
- Reunion records, Accession 1986-A-086
  - Correspondence and news notes regarding the Class of 1907 S and its secretary Warner S. Hayes (Misty), 1963-1970 (Box 1)